do you need term insurance
if you just got married or recently
become a parent
you must buy term insurance today
and financially secure your spouse child
or parents in your absence this
also ensures that liabilities like emis
for home loans
card loans etc are taken care of
and your child's future education
monthly family expenses
do not suffer if you are single
and do not have any dependents you may
not need a term insurance now
but a new age term plan like icici brew
eye protect smart
gives you option to cover your health
against
34 critical illnesses like cancer
heart attack etc so don't delay
and secure yourself and your family with
term insurance plan
today